http://www.irishwhitewater.com/privacy.php

Privacy Policy - Irish WhiteWater - Ireland's river guide for kayaking and canoeing
IWW Race League
River UpdatesOwenshagh13/01/2017Avonmore (Clara Vale Section)18/07/2015Tourmakeady Waterfall06/04/2015Owenass ("The Catholes")30/08/2014Upper Derg 30/08/2014 Add a River
Latest PhotosBoyne 07/01/2019 Owenroe 11/11/2018 Ow 05/01/2016 Owenroe 29/12/2015 Glenarm 03/01/2015
Random Photo
IrishwhitWater.com Privacy Policy
Just a whole lot of web related legal stuff that I have to show just to cover my ass. There is nothing sinister in it, it's just how IrishWhiteWater.com (and lots of other sites like playak.com or irishfreesytle.com) treat your data (IP addresses, email address, etc. etc.). We will not sell your email address!
Website Visitors
Except as described below, the IrishWhiteWater.com does not collect or require visitors to its Web sites to furnish personally-identifying information such as names, email addresses and phone numbers.
Like most Web site operators, IrishWhiteWater.com does collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and date and time of each visitor request.
IrishWhiteWater.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, which are non-personally-identifying in and of themselves but could be used in conjunction with other information to personally identify users.
IrishWhiteWater.com's purpose in collecting this information is to better understand how IrishWhiteWater.com's visitors use its Web sites.
To that end, IrishWhiteWater.com may share potentially personally-identifying information with its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations.
IrishWhiteWater.com may also release non-personally-identifying information about visitors, e.g. by publishing a report on Web site usage trends.
Otherwise, IrishWhiteWater.com will not publicly release potentially personally-identifying information except under the same circumstances as IrishWhiteWater.com releases personally-identifying information.
Those circumstances are explained in detail below.
Community Members
Users are advised not to submit any sensitive information such as credit card numbers, social security numbers, maps to buried treasure, etc, to Irishwhitwater.com.... Yaar.
Certain members of the IrishWhiteWater.com community (contributors, customers, etc.) choose to interact with IrishWhiteWater.com in ways that require IrishWhiteWater.com and others to know more about them.
The amount and type of information that IrishWhiteWater.com gathers from those members depends on the nature of the interaction.
For example, members who wish to post content to certain portions of IrishWhiteWater.com's Web sites are asked to provide usernames that identify that content as having been posted by a particular member.
Developers, by comparison, are asked to provide contact information, up to and sometimes including telephone or fax numbers, so that they can be contacted as necessary.
Customers of the IrishWhiteWater.com store are asked to provide even more information, including billing and shipping addresses and credit card or similar information.
In each case, IrishWhiteWater.com collects personally-identifying information only insofar as is necessary to fulfill the purpose of the community member's interaction with IrishWhiteWater.com.
IrishWhiteWater.com is an open organization that believes in sharing as much information as possible about its products, its operations and its associations.
Accordingly, community members should assume - as should most folks who interact with IrishWhiteWater.com - that any personally-identifying information provided to IrishWhiteWater.com will be made available to the public.
There are three broad exceptions to that rule:
IrishWhiteWater.com does not publicly release information gathered in connection with commercial transactions (i.e., transactions involving money), including transactions conducted through the IrishWhiteWater.com Store.
IrishWhiteWater.com does not make publicly available information that is used to authenticate users the publication of which would compromise the security of IrishWhiteWater.com's Web sites (e.g., passwords).
IrishWhiteWater.com does not make publicly available information that it specifically promises at the time of collection to maintain in confidence.
Outside those three contexts, users should assume that personally-identifying information provided through IrishWhiteWater.com's Web sites will be made available to the public.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a Web site stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the Web site each time the visitor returns.
IrishWhiteWater.com's Web sites use cookies to help IrishWhiteWater.com identify and track visitors, their usage of IrishWhiteWater.com Web sites, and their Web site access preferences across multiple requests and visits to IrishWhiteWater.com's Web sites.
It is possible to link cookies to personally-identifying information, thereby permitting Web site operators to track the online movements of particular individuals.
IrishWhiteWater.com, however, does not do so.
Instead, it uses the information provided by cookies to develop a better understanding of how IrishWhiteWater.com's visitors use, and to facilitate those visitors' interactions with, IrishWhiteWater.com's Web sites.
IrishWhiteWater.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers by IrishWhiteWater.com or its contractors should set their browsers to refuse cookies before linking to IrishWhiteWater.com's Web sites.
Certain features of IrishWhiteWater.com's Web sites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Where IrishWhiteWater.com has collected personally-identifying information subject to one of the three exceptions described in the Contributors and Customers section, above, it discloses that information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to process it on IrishWhiteWater.com's behalf and that have agreed not to disclose it to others.
Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using IrishWhiteWater.com's Web sites, you consent to the transfer of your information to them.
IrishWhiteWater.com does not rent or sell such information to anyone.
Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, IrishWhiteWater.com discloses such information only when required to do so by law, or when IrishWhiteWater.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of IrishWhiteWater.com, members of the IrishWhiteWater.com community, or the public at large.
IrishWhiteWater.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of such information
Privacy Policy Changes
Although changes are likely to be minor, IrishWhiteWater.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time.
Any and all changes will be reflected on this page.
About |
Site Map | Privacy Policy | Disclaimer |
Contact Us |
| ©2009 IrishWhitewater.com
